Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - J
        - Jackson, Mahalia - Silent night-songs for Christmas, 1962; SR-16142; Jackson, Mahalia (Box 305)
          Catalog # 3C 38304; A-side Matrix # AL 38304 G18
        - Jackson, Mahalia - Christmas with Mahalia, 1968; SR-16143; Jackson, Mahalia (Box 305)
          Catalog # CS 9727; A-side Matrix # XSM-138022 G2B XG GIP
        - Jackson, Marlon - (Let your love find) The chosen one, 1986; SR-16144; Jackson, Marlon (Box 305)
          Catalog # V-15277; A-side Matrix # V-1-15277-100541B-100541A-Z2
        - Jackson, Michael - Thriller, 1982; SR-16145; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-16146. Different discs.
          Catalog # QE 38112; A-side Matrix # PAL 38112-1E
        - Jackson, Michael - Thriller, 1982; SR-16146; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-16145. Different discs.
          Catalog # QE 38112; A-side Matrix # PAL 38112-1C
        - Jackson, Michael - HIStory (Mark Picchiotti mixes), 1997; SR-16147; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # XPR 3149; A-side Matrix # 31 3149 20 1A1
        - Jackson, Michael - Blood on the dance floor, 1997; SR-16148; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # 664462 6; A-side Matrix # U1 664355 20 1A1
          The Netherlands
        - Jackson, Michael - Remember the time, 1992; SR-16149; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # 49 74201; A-side Matrix # XSS 74201A-1B
        - Jackson, Michael - Dangerous (Disc one), 1991; SR-16150; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-16151. Double album.
          Catalog # E 48841; A-side Matrix # PAL 48841-1B
        - Jackson, Michael - Dangerous (Disc two), 1991; SR-16151; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-16150. Double album.
          Catalog # E 48842; A-side Matrix # PAL 48842-1B
        - Jackson, Michael - Michael, 2002; SR-16152; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # PTR3001; A-side Matrix # CM101-A
        - Jackson, Michael - The EP, 2002; SR-16153; Jackson, Michael; Knuckles, Frankie (Box 305)
          Catalog # XPPR7057; A-side Matrix # MJ-003 A
        - Jackson, Michael - Blood on the dance floor; History in the mix, 1997; SR-16154; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # E2 68070; A-side Matrix # PAL 68070-A
        - Jackson, Michael - Earth song, 1995; SR-16155; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # 662569 6; A-side Matrix # 01 662569 20 1A1
        - Jackson, Michael - Ghosts (Mousse T. mixes), 1997; SR-16156; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # XPR 3160; A-side Matrix # 31 3160 20 1A1
        - Jackson, Michael - Wanna be startin' somethin', 1983; SR-16157; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # 49-03915; A-side Matrix # XSS-169321-1B
        - Jackson, Michael - Blood on the dance floor, 1997; SR-17961; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17962. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49 78008; A-side Matrix # XSS 78008A-1A
        - Jackson, Michael - Blood on the dance floor, 1997; SR-17962; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17961. 2 copies.
        - Jackson, Michael - Live!, 1988; SR-17963; Jackson, Michael; Jackson 5 (Box 305)
          Catalog # WL 72461; A-side Matrix # DMG-2963 A-1/6-88
          Germany
        - Jackson, Michael - Beat it, 1983; SR-17964; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # AS 1624; A-side Matrix # XSS-169234-A
        - Jackson, Michael - Smooth criminal, 1988; SR-17965; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # 49 07895; A-side Matrix # XSS-07895A-2A
        - Jackson, Michael - HIStory (Tony Moran mixes), 1997; SR-17966; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # XPR 3159; A-side Matrix # 31 3159 20 1A1
        - Jackson, Michael - Rock with you, 1979; SR-17967; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # AS 687; A-side Matrix # XSS 166449-1B
        - Jackson, Michael - Thriller, 1984; SR-17968; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17969. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AS 1805; A-side Matrix # XSS-169545-1A
        - Jackson, Michael - Thriller, 1984; SR-17969; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17968. 2 copies.
        - Jackson, Michael - Wanna be startin' somethin', 1983; SR-17970; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
        - Jackson, Michael - Billie Jean, 1982; SR-17971; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17972. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 1596; A-side Matrix # XSS-169204-1A
        - Jackson, Michael - Billie Jean, 1983; SR-17972; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17971. Different discs.
          Catalog # 49 03557; A-side Matrix # XSS-169204 1A
        - Jackson, Michael - Michael, 2003; SR-17973; Jackson, Michael (Box 305)
          Catalog # PTR3002; A-side Matrix # PTR-3002-A
          Coin Flip Records
        - Jackson, Mick - Rock the world (No other girl), 1986; SR-17974; Jackson, Mick (Box 305)
          Catalog # FMS 62257; A-side Matrix # FMS-62257-A
          Select Records
        - Jackson, Millie - "Live and outrageous" (Rated XXX), 1982; SR-17975; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # SP-1-6735; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6735-AS-HRM-2
          Spring Records
        - Jackson, Millie - I had to say it, 1980; SR-17976; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # PRO 146; A-side Matrix # PRO-146-80-NP-5402-BLEEPED-PW1
        - Jackson, Millie - You knocked the love (Right outta my heart), 1988; SR-17977; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # 1194-1-JDAC; A-side Matrix # 11941 JD A
          Jive
        - Jackson, Millie - Millie Jackson, 1972; SR-17978; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # SEW 009; A-side Matrix # DMC-7787 A-1/4-89
          Southbound
        - Jackson, Millie - I got to try it one time, 1974; SR-17979; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # SEW 023; A-side Matrix # DMD-2527 A-1/1-90
        - Jackson, Millie - We got to hit it off, 1979; SR-17980; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # PRO-099; A-side Matrix # SP D 403 79NP S K1 PRO 099
        - Jackson, Millie - Caught up, 1974; SR-17981; Jackson, Millie (Box 305)
          Catalog # SEW 003; A-side Matrix # DMC 7330 A-3/4-89
        - Jackson, Paul, Jr. - I came to play, 1988; SR-17982; Jackson, Paul, Jr. (Box 305)
          Catalog # DMD 1160; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-54346-1
        - Jackson, Paul, Jr. - I came to play, 1988; SR-17983; Jackson, Paul, Jr. (Box 305)
        - Jackson, R. Lee - Special request, SR-17984; Jackson, R. Lee (Box 305)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # B2SP-IC-0005-A
          I Culture International
        - Jackson, Rebbie - R U tuff enuff, 1988; SR-17985; Jackson, Rebbie (Box 305)
          Catalog # 44 07813; A-side Matrix # XSS-177786 C1 G1
        - Jackson, Rebbie - Plaything, 1987; SR-17986; Jackson, Rebbie (Box 305)
          Catalog # 44 07560; A-side Matrix # XSS-177514-1B
        - Jackson, Rebbie - Reaction, 1986; SR-17987; Jackson, Rebbie (Box 305)
          Catalog # 44-05927; A-side Matrix # XSS-175263-1B
        - Jacksons - Shake your body (Down to the ground); Blame it on the boogie, 1978; SR-17988; Jacksons (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17989. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 12E4-8307; A-side Matrix # 8307-A-1A-2HZ
        - Jacksons - Shake your body (Down to the ground); Blame it on the boogie, 1978; SR-17989; Jacksons (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17988. 2 copies.
        - Jacksons - Heartbreak hotel, 1981; SR-17990; Jacksons (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17991; SR-17992. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 1351; A-side Matrix # XSS-168379-1D
        - Jacksons - Live (Disc one), 1981; SR-17991; Jacksons (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17990; SR-17992. Double album; Different discs.
          Catalog # KE2 37545; A-side Matrix # PAL-37546-1F
        - Jacksons - Live (Disc two), 1981; SR-17992; Jacksons (Box 305)
          In same jacket as # SR-17990; SR-17991. Double album; Different discs.
          Catalog # KE2 37545; A-side Matrix # PAL-37547-1H
        - Jacksons - Time out for the burglar (12" extended version), 1987; SR-17993; Jacksons (Box 305)
          Catalog # MCA-23729; A-side Matrix # MCA-6644-FDS-2
          MCA Records
        - Jacksons - Shake your body (Down to the ground), 1978; SR-17994; Jacksons (Box 305)
          Catalog # 28-50721; A-side Matrix # XSS-165162-1D
        - Jacksons - Triumph, 1980; SR-17995; Jacksons (Box 305)
          Catalog # AL 36424; A-side Matrix # PAL-36424-1AK
        - Jacksons - Body, 1984; SR-17996; Jacksons (Box 305)
          Catalog # AS 1954; A-side Matrix # XSS 169838-1A
        - Jacobs-Rock, Debbie - Doctor music, 1983; SR-17997; Jacobs-Rock, Debbie (Box 305)
          Catalog # P-49803; A-side Matrix # P-49803-AX
          Personal Records
        - Jade - 5-4-3-2 (Yo! Time is up), 1994; SR-17998; Jade (Box 305)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7117; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 7117 SR1
          Giant Records
        - Jade, Jason Juston - (Disco) Hokey pokey, 1979; SR-17999; Jade, Jason Juston (Box 305)
          Catalog # TCD-87-DJ; A-side Matrix # TCD-87-AS-A-3
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Jae-Ski - Bad to the bone, 1988; SR-18000; Jae-Ski (Box 306)
          Catalog # SF88100; A-side Matrix # SF88100-A
          State Of Fresh Records
        - Jagged Edge - The way that you talk, 1997; SR-18001; Jagged Edge; Da Brat; JD (Box 306)
          Catalog # CAS 0777; A-side Matrix # XSS-0777A-1B
        - Jagged Edge - Keys to the range, 1999; SR-18002; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
          Catalog # CAS 42463; A-side Matrix # XSS-42463-A-3
        - Jagged Edge - Let's get married (Disc one), 1999; SR-18003; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18004. Double album.
          Catalog # CS 79462; A-side Matrix # XSS-79462A-1A
        - Jagged Edge - Let's get married (Disc two), 1999; SR-18004; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18003. Double album.
          Catalog # CS 79463; A-side Matrix # XSS-79463B-1B
        - Jagged Edge - He can't love you, 1999; SR-18005; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44 79323; A-side Matrix # XSS-79323 A
        - Jagged Edge - The way that you talk, 1997; SR-18006; Jagged Edge; Da Brat; JD (Box 306)
        - Jagged Edge - The way that you talk, 1997; SR-18007; Jagged Edge; Da Brat; JD (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44 78640; A-side Matrix # XSS-78640A-1B
        - Jagged Edge - Where the party at, 2001; SR-18008; Jagged Edge; Dupri, Jermaine; Nelly (Box 306)
          Catalog # CAS 16899; A-side Matrix # XSS 16899 A
        - Jagged Edge - The way that you talk, 1997; SR-18009; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
          Catalog # CAS 3439; A-side Matrix # XSS 3439-A
        - Jagged Edge - The way that you talk, 1997; SR-18010; Jagged Edge (Box 306)
        - Jagged Edge - Where the party at, 2001; SR-18011; Jagged Edge; Nelly (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44 79605; A-side Matrix # XSS 79605 A
        - Jagger, Mick - Ruthless people, 1986; SR-18012; Jagger, Mick (Box 306)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # 49-05931; A-side Matrix # XSS-175292-1B
        - Jagger, Mick - Lucky in love, 1985; SR-18013; Jagger, Mick (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44-05214; A-side Matrix # XXS-174352-1A
        - Jagger, Mick - Primitive cool, 1987; SR-18014; Jagger, Mick (Box 306)
          Catalog # OC 40919; A-side Matrix # AL40919-1COMM G
        - Jagger, Mick - She's the boss, 1985; SR-18015; Jagger, Mick (Box 306)
          Catalog # FC 39940; A-side Matrix # AL-39940-1G
        - Jagwarr, Don - Faded, 1994; SR-18016; Jagwarr, Don; Ice Cube; 2Pac (Box 306)
          Catalog # P1 53926; A-side Matrix # P1-53926-A S-30264
          Priority Records
        - Jah Mikey - Peace in the Middle East, SR-18017; Jah Mikey; Jay Kid; El Mayoral (Box 306)
          Catalog # CT108LP; A-side Matrix # CT-108-LP-A
          Cartone Records
        - Jah Shaka - Dub symphony, 1990; SR-18018; Jah Shaka (Box 306)
          Catalog # 539 884-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-884-1-A-SP
          Mango
        - Jaheim - Fabulous, 2002; SR-18019; Jaheim (Box 306)
          Catalog # PRO-A-101038; A-side Matrix # PROA101038-A-SR1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Jaheim - Could it be, 2001; SR-18020; Jaheim (Box 306)
          Catalog # 0-44983; A-side Matrix # 0-44983-A-SR1
        - Jahneen - Love boy, 1994; SR-18021; Jahneen (Box 306)
          Catalog # sr-01; A-side Matrix # SR-01-A
          Soundstorm Publishing
        - Jahneen - Dr. Slumber, 1986; SR-18022; Jahneen (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18023. 2 copies.
          Catalog # KS101; A-side Matrix # KS-101-A
          Kalidescope Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Jahneen - Dr. slumber, 1986; SR-18023; Jahneen (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18022. 2 copies.
        - Jahsir - Gotta push up; Pushin' up; What I did do, SR-18024; Jahsir (Box 306)
          Catalog # BBM 021; A-side Matrix # BBM-021-A
          Big Brother Music
          Hackensack, New Jersey
        - Jai, Rikki - Show me your motion, SR-18025; Jai, Rikki (Box 306)
          Catalog # S.I.0012; A-side Matrix # SI 0015 A
          Spice Island Records
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Jai, Rikki - Wild and rough, 1990; SR-18026; Jai, Rikki (Box 306)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # SI 0010 B
          The Music Lab
          Trinidad & Tobago
        - Jak - I go wild, 1985; SR-18027; Jak (Box 306)
          Catalog # 49-05149; A-side Matrix # XSS 169890-1B
        - JaKKi - Got me burnin' up, 1982; SR-18028; JaKKi (Box 306)
          Catalog # RT-1001; A-side Matrix # RT-101-A
          RedTown
        - Jakky Boy & The Bad Bunch - Eye to eye; Talking Japanese, 1985; SR-18029; Jakky Boy & The Bad Bunch (Box 306)
          Catalog # DMD 923; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49105-1
        - Jalea - Tu suenos, SR-18030; Jalea; YMA America (Box 306)
          Catalog # LOC 298 R; A-side Matrix # LOC 298R-A1
        - Jam - Town called malice; Precious, 1982; SR-18031; Jam (Box 306)
          Catalog # POSPX 400; A-side Matrix # POSP 400
        - Jam - Town called malice, 1982; SR-18032; Jam (Box 306)
          Catalog # PRO 180; A-side Matrix # PRO 180 82 NP-5872-PRC-C-1-1
        - Jam D.O.T. - Soul search'n (Remix); Time, 1996; SR-18033; Jam D.O.T. (Box 306)
          Catalog # F002; A-side Matrix # F-002-A
          456 Records
          Queens, New York
        - Jamaica Boys - Move it!, 1990; SR-18034; Jamaica Boys (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18035. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-4316; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-4316-SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Queen Mother Rage - Slipping into darkness, 1990; SR-18035; Queen Mother Rage (Box 306)
          In same jacket as # SR-18034. Different discs.
          Catalog # 3-4004-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # 3-4004-0 RE1 A
          Cardiac Records
        - Jamaica Boys - Shake it up!, 1990; SR-18036; Jamaica Boys (Box 306)
          Catalog # 0-21463; A-side Matrix # 0-21463A-SR1
        - Jamaica Girls - Need somebody new, 1983; SR-18037; Jamaica Girls (Box 306)
          Catalog # SLX-005; A-side Matrix # SLX-005
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Jamaica Girls - Rock the beat, 1982; SR-18038; Jamaica Girls (Box 306)
          Catalog # BKD 511; A-side Matrix # BKD-511-A
          Becket Records
        - Jamaica Girls - Rock the beat, 1982; SR-18039; Jamaica Girls (Box 306)
        - Jamaica Girls - Need somebody new, 1983; SR-18040; Jamaica Girls (Box 306)
        - Jamal - Fades em all, 1995; SR-18041; Jamal (Box 306)
          Catalog # 75444-35043-1; A-side Matrix # 75444-35043-1A-SP1
          Rowdy Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Jamal - Keep it real; Unf***wittable, 1996; SR-18042; Jamal (Box 306)
          Catalog # RDP-5067; A-side Matrix # 75444-35067-1-A1
        - Jamal-Ski - Jump, spread out, 1994; SR-18043; Jamal-Ski (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44 77374; A-side Matrix # XSS-77374-B-1A
        - Jamal-Ski - Jump, spread out, 1994; SR-18044; Jamal-Ski (Box 306)
        - Jamal-Ski - A piece of reality, 1992; SR-18045; Jamal-Ski (Box 306)
          Catalog # 44 74780; A-side Matrix # XSS-74780-A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records
        - James, Bob - Two, 1985; SR-18046; James, Bob (Box 306)
          Catalog # PC 36836; A-side Matrix # AL-36836 G2C
          Tappan Zee Records
        - James, Bob - BJ4, 1977; SR-18047; James, Bob (Box 306)
          Catalog # CTI 7074; A-side Matrix # RVG 87735-A-8
          CTI Records
        - James, Boney - Sweet thing; I still dream, 1997; SR-18048; James, Boney (Box 306)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8776; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8776-A-SR1
        - James, Boney - The night I fell in love, 1995; SR-18049; James, Boney (Box 306)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7212; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7212-A-SR1
        - James, Boney - Creepin', 1992; SR-18050; James, Boney (Box 306)
          Catalog # 0-41995; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7409-A-RE1-DMM-SR1/0-41995-A-DMM-SR1
        - James, Elsworth - Tribute to Ben Johnson, 1989; SR-18051; James, Elsworth (Box 307)
          Catalog # RDR12; A-side Matrix # RDR12-1-A
          Soca Village Records
          Toronto, Canada
        - James, Etta - R & B dynamite, 1987; SR-18052; James, Etta (Box 307)
          Catalog # CH 210; A-side Matrix # CH 210 A 020 B-7906A-1
          Ace
        - James, Etta - Sings funk, 1970; SR-18053; James, Etta (Box 307)
          Catalog # X5RS-5389; A-side Matrix # X5RS-5389-1
          Cadet Records
        - James, Freddie - Hollywood, 1979; SR-18054; James, Freddie (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO-A1-833; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-833-S-A1
        - James, Freddie - Hot thing, 1983; SR-18055; James, Freddie (Box 307)
          Catalog # AD 1 9052; A-side Matrix # AD-1-9052-SA
        - James, Freddie - Don't turn your back on love, 1982; SR-18056; James, Freddie (Box 307)
          Catalog # CP 716; A-side Matrix # CP-716-SA
        - James, Freddie - Crazy disco music, 1979; SR-18057; James, Freddie (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO-A-844; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-844-S-A1
        - James, John - She bought love, 1988; SR-18058; James, John (Box 307)
          Catalog # ATT 2001; A-side Matrix # ATT 2001-A
          Attic
        - James, Jimmy - Dancin' till dawn, 1980; SR-18059; James, Jimmy (Box 307)
          Catalog # 4.14.404.111; A-side Matrix # 4.14-404-111-A
          Pye Records
          Brazil
        - James, Rick - Street songs, 1981; SR-18060; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # G8-1002M1; A-side Matrix # G8-1002M1-A-153
          Gordy
        - James, Rick - She blew my mind (69 times), 1982; SR-18061; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # PR-107; A-side Matrix # PR-107-A-66551-D-15-A
        - James, Rick - You and I, 1978; SR-18062; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # PR-34; A-side Matrix # PR-34-65172-D-RE1 13C PKA
        - James, Rick - Fire it up, 1979; SR-18063; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # G8-990MI; A-side Matrix # G 8990 MI (A)
        - James, Rick - Glow, 1985; SR-18064; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # 6135GL; A-side Matrix # 6135-GL-A-15B ZEA
        - James, Rick - Wonderful, 1988; SR-18065; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # 0-20994; A-side Matrix # 0-20994-A
        - James, Rick - Forever and a day, 1986; SR-18066; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # 4565 GG; A-side Matrix # 4565-GGA-67597-15B ZBW
        - James, Rick - Come get it!, 1978; SR-18067; James, Rick (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18068; SR-18069. 2 copies; different discs.
          Catalog # G7-981R1; A-side Matrix # G7-981R1 2807-13A
        - James, Rick - Come get it!, 1978; SR-18068; James, Rick (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18067; SR-18069. 2 copies; different discs.
        - Mary Jane Girls - All night long, 1983; SR-18069; Mary Jane Girls (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18067; SR-18068. Different discs; 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR 118; A-side Matrix # PR-118-A-66805-D-15A
        - James, Rick - Loosey's rap, 1988; SR-18070; James, Rick; Shante, Roxanne; Big Daddy Kane (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18071. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20941; A-side Matrix # 0-20941-RE1-SR1
        - James, Rick - Loosey's rap, 1988; SR-18071; James, Rick; Shante, Roxanne; Big Daddy Kane (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18070. 2 copies.
        - James, Rick - Give it to me baby, 1979; SR-18072; James, Rick (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18073. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TMGLTD 20; A-side Matrix # TMGLTD-20-A
        - James, Rick - Give it to me baby, 1979; SR-18073; James, Rick (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18072. 2 copies.
        - James, Rick - Reflections, 1984; SR-18074; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # 6095GL; A-side Matrix # GL-6095-A-15C ZHQ
        - James, Rick - Sweet and sexy thing (Special 12" remix), 1986; SR-18075; James, Rick (Box 307)
          Catalog # 4561 GG; A-side Matrix # 4561-GGA-67566-15B ZBL
        - James, TC - Get up on your feet (Keep on dancin'), 1978; SR-18076; James, TC; Fist-O-Funk Orchestra (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18077. Different discs.
          Catalog # F-O-F 947; A-side Matrix # FOF 947-A
          Fist-O-Funk
          Pomona, New York
        - James, TC - Dance all over the world, 1978; SR-18077; James, TC; Fist-O-Funk Orchestra (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18076. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # F-O-F 1947; A-side Matrix # FOF-1947A
        - Jamestown - She got soul, 1991; SR-18078; Jamestown; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 307)
          Catalog # AMYDJ 819; A-side Matrix # AMYDJ 819 A-1J-1-1
        - Jamestown - She got soul, 1991; SR-18079; Jamestown; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 307)
        - Jamiroquai - Space cowboy, 1995; SR-18080; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          Catalog # 42 77827; A-side Matrix # XSS77827A-1B
          Work
        - Jamiroquai - Deeper underground - remixes by Roger Sanchez, 1998; SR-18081; Jamiroquai; Sanchez, Roger (Box 307)
          Catalog # EAS 41375; A-side Matrix # XSS-41375A-1A
          Epic Dance
        - Jamiroquai - Emergency on planet Earth, 1993; SR-18082; Jamiroquai; Tenaglia, Danny (Box 307)
          Catalog # CAS 6102; A-side Matrix # XSS77529A-1A
        - Jamiroquai - Traveling without moving (Disc one), 1996; SR-18083; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18084. Double album.
          Catalog # 483999 1; A-side Matrix # 01 483999 20 1A1
          Sony Soho Square
        - Jamiroquai - Traveling without moving (Disc two), 1996; SR-18084; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18083. Double album.
          Catalog # 483999 1; A-side Matrix # 01 483999 20 1C1
        - Jamiroquai - Emergency on planet Earth (Masters at work remixes), 1993; SR-18085; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          Catalog # XPR 2061; A-side Matrix # XPR-2601-A
        - Jamiroquai - Alright, 1997; SR-18086; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          Catalog # 664235 6; A-side Matrix # 01 664235 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - The return of the space cowboy (Disc one), 1994; SR-18087; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18088. Double album.
          Catalog # 477813 1; A-side Matrix # 01 477813 20 1A1
        - Jamiroquai - The return of the space cowboy (Disc two), 1994; SR-18088; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          In same jacket as # SR-18087. Double album.
          Catalog # 477813 1; A-side Matrix # 01 477813 20 1C1
        - Jamiroquai - Emergency on planet Earth, 1993; SR-18089; Jamiroquai (Box 307)
          Catalog # CAS 6102; A-side Matrix # XSS77529-1